<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Call of Red Mountain</string>
    <string name="edit_message">Enter a message</string>
    <string name="button_nif_display">Nif Display</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="kfdisplaytext">Kf Display</string>
    <string name="jbulletdisplaytext">JBullet Display</string>
    <string name="esexplorertext">Explore</string>
    <string name="directory_selected_label">selected directory</string>
    <string name="btn_choose">Choose</string>
    <string name="none">none</string>
    <string name="setgameesmfile">Set Game Data File</string>
    <string name="welcometext" formatted="false"><![CDATA[<html>
    <p>
Call of Red Mountain uses the assets from Morrowind by Bethesda Game Studios (2002).<br>
In order to play this game you must have acquired those files in some manner, they are not distributed with this game engine.<br>
Please copy the Morrowind installation folder onto your device now, this can be up to 1.2Gb or more so you will need plenty of sdcard space.<br>
You can copy it to any location that is accessible from your computer\'s file explorer.<br>
There is an video of how to do this here:<br>
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q_MmQSTznh4">Call or Red Mountain setup demonstration</a><br>
</p>
<p>
When you first start up Call of Red Mountain you will be asked to select the Morrowind.esm file that is located in that game installation folder
on your device. From there the game engine will locate the other asset files relative to that esm file. <br>
The controls of Call of Red Mountain are not refined and so may take a little getting used to.<br>
The screen of your device is divided into 4 squares, in half horizontally and in half vertically<br>
The lower left is the walk controls, similar to W S A D on a keyboard, so your character will walk forward when you press in the
upper portion of the lower left square, backward when touched in the lower portion and strafe side to side when touched on either side.<br>
The lower right square acts similarly to the mouse on a computer, so dragging around in this area will make the view rotate.<br>
Either of the upper squares simply activates whatever is in front of you (and highlighted), so gates will open and travel doors will be activated.<br>
</p>
<p>
There are several pre-set start locations and configurations, or you can use the in game options menu to warp around.<br>
</p>
<p>
To show the keyboard swipe up in the top half of the screen.
To change options in game, show the keyboard, then press o
If you want to fly, show the keyboard, then press f
In free-fly mode press on the left side of the upper portion of the screen to go up or down.
</p>
<p>If you have some time and own the game Oblivion you could attempt to build a converted texture file and play it<br>
To do that please follow these instructions:<br>
<a href="https://www.dropbox.com/s/s6mc0tzt1u6pv3d/CoRM%20texture%20conversion.zip?dl=0">CoRM texture conversion</a>
]]></string>
    <string name="welcometextyes">Remind me later</string>
    <string name="welcometextno">Don\'t remind me</string>
    <string name="wait_file_download">file downloading</string>
    <string name="capturelogs">Write log</string>
    <string name="dontcapturelogs">Don\'t write log</string>
    <string name="menu_test_3d">Test 3D</string>
    <string name="menu_help">Help</string>
    <string name="menu_about">About</string>
    <string name="menu_donate">Donate</string>
    <string name="menu_deoptomize">Deoptomize</string>
    <string name="menu_anti_alias">x2 AA</string>
    <string name="donations__description">Do you love Morrowind?\nAny support would be gratefully appreciated and may assist in speeding up development!</string>
    <string name="menu_options">Options</string>
    <string name="menu_start_tools">Start Tools</string>
    <string-array name="donation_google_catalog_values">
        <item>Donation 1</item>
        <item>Donation 2</item>
        <item>Donation 5</item>
        <item>Donation 10</item>
        <item>Donation 20</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>